{
  "user": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "username": "student",
      "password": "student123"
    }
  ],
  "quiz": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "2 + 2 - 2 = ?",
      "option": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "3",
        "4"
      ],
      "ans": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "5 * 2 - 3 = ?",
      "option": [
        "7",
        "8",
        "9",
        "10"
      ],
      "ans": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "10 / 2 + 3 = ?",
      "option": [
        "3",
        "5",
        "6",
        "8"
      ],
      "ans": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "8 - 3 + 4 = ?",
      "option": [
        "7",
        "8",
        "9",
        "10"
      ],
      "ans": "9"
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "6 * 3 - 5 = ?",
      "option": [
        "11",
        "13",
        "15",
        "18"
      ],
      "ans": "13"
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "9 + 1 - 5 = ?",
      "option": [
        "3",
        "4",
        "5",
        "6"
      ],
      "ans": "5"
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "12 / 3 + 2 = ?",
      "option": [
        "4",
        "5",
        "6",
        "7"
      ],
      "ans": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "7 * 2 - 8 = ?",
      "option": [
        "2",
        "4",
        "6",
        "8"
      ],
      "ans": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "15 - 3 * 3 = ?",
      "option": [
        "3",
        "6",
        "9",
        "12"
      ],
      "ans": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "4 * 2 + 1 = ?",
      "option": [
        "6",
        "7",
        "8",
        "9"
      ],
      "ans": "9"
    }
  ]
}